{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Security System Repair Services","appliedActionRules":{"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719":"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719_ctrl"},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","__cache./api/resource/task/40137/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40137,"taskName":"Alarm or Security System - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair an Alarm or Security System","xmTaskDescriptor":"Security System Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":1400,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Alarm surveillance secure safe System","textMessagingName":"Repr Alarm","rolloverLongDesc":"These companies will diagnose \u0026 repair problems with existing security systems. Note separate categories for cameras, guards, monitoring \u0026 installation.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes burglar, fire, smoke, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair an Alarm or Security System.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Home Security \u0026 Alarm System Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":67,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Alarm System Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Alarm or Security System - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Security System Project","urlName":"Alarm-or-Security-System-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Home Security/Alarm Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"Alarm,surveillance,secure,safe,System,burglar,alarms,protect,protection,Security","emcCategoryOid":-12043,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":448,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40137/":{"taskOID":40137,"originalTaskOID":40137,"setID":448,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4016,"questionDisplayText":"Describe problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the  problem(s) with your security system.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2373,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"False alarm","answerDisplayText":"False alarm","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2398,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Faulty window or door security","answerDisplayText":"Faulty window or door security","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2244,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Entry key pad isn't working","answerDisplayText":"Entry key pad isn't working","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6807,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Want to change programming or codes","answerDisplayText":"Want to change programming or codes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6810,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Want to expand my system","answerDisplayText":"Want to expand my system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5137,"questionDisplayText":"Who installed system","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Who installed the system?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4927,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Professional","answerDisplayText":"Professional","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1602,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Consumer","answerDisplayText":"Consumer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4016,"questionDisplayText":"Describe problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the  problem(s) with your security system.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2373,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"False alarm","answerDisplayText":"False alarm","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2398,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Faulty window or door security","answerDisplayText":"Faulty window or door security","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2244,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Entry key pad isn't working","answerDisplayText":"Entry key pad isn't working","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6807,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Want to change programming or codes","answerDisplayText":"Want to change programming or codes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6810,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Want to expand my system","answerDisplayText":"Want to expand my system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2373,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"False alarm","answerDisplayText":"False alarm","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2398,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Faulty window or door security","answerDisplayText":"Faulty window or door security","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2244,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Entry key pad isn't working","answerDisplayText":"Entry key pad isn't working","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6807,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Want to change programming or codes","answerDisplayText":"Want to change programming or codes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6810,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Want to expand my system","answerDisplayText":"Want to expand my system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5137,"questionDisplayText":"Who installed system","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Who installed the system?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4927,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Professional","answerDisplayText":"Professional","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1602,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Consumer","answerDisplayText":"Consumer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4927,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Professional","answerDisplayText":"Professional","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1602,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Consumer","answerDisplayText":"Consumer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}